A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Quality of Care for Underserved Populations, SG 3, Series 5 FA1462
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Quality of Care for Underserved Populations, SG 3, Series 5
1992-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1462
6.85 Cubic Feet 15 letter-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box.
Arrangement
Records are in original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was transferred to RAC as accession 2007:077 and Accession 2002:109.
Scope and Contents
This series documents the Commonwealth Fund Quality of Care for Underserved Populations program, including the Commonwealth Fund Minority Health Survey. The majority of the material is grant administration files. These records often include documentation of: proposals, administration and budget, grant products, related correspondence and background material. A limited selection of meeting records and program files is also included.
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Briefing Book, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Grant Products, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Grant Products, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Grant Products (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Background Information (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Survey Development, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Reviewer Comments (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Background Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Press Articles on Findings (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Press Packets (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Press Release, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Survey Information Packet, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Administration Files - Survey Dissemination Activities, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Grant Products - Final Report, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Follow-Up, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Background Information and Articles (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Administration and Budget, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Consultants Papers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Minority Health Survey (94-63) - Materials from David Williams (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy 2001 - Fourth Annual Meeting, 2001 May 9-10 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
- Commonwealth Fund-Harvard University Fellowship in Minority Health Policy 2001 - Fourth Annual Meeting (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Site Visit to Meharry Medical College, 1994 July 6 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Conference Materials (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Background Information (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Administration and Budget, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Meeting the Needs of Minority Communities (93-40) - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- National Medical Fellowships - An Evaluation of the Fellowship Program in Academic Medicine for Minority Students (11234), 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- National Medical Fellowships - An Evaluation of the Fellowship Program in Academic Medicine for Minority Students (11234) - Grant Products, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
- Meharry Medical College - Developing a Health Services Strategic Plan (95-20) - Administration and Budget, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
- Meharry Medical College - Developing a Health Services Strategic Plan (95-20) - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Meharry Medical College - Developing a Health Services Strategic Plan (95-20) - Articles and Background (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Meharry Medical College - Developing a Health Services Strategic Plan (95-20) - Grant Products - Site Visit to Meharry, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- Louis Harris and Associates - Physicians Attitudes Toward and Experiences with Managed Care: Oversampling of Minority Physicians, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- National Black Caucus of State Legislators - A Compendium of Resources for Elected Officials (96656) (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
- Medicaid - HBCU Public-Private Partnership Proposals, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- National Black Caucus of State Legislators - A Compendium of Resources for Elected Officials (96656) (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
- Columbia University - Pardes - Regionalization of Selected Services to Northern Manhattan (970299), 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies - Williams - Forum on the Future of Public Hospitals, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
- Morehouse School of Medicine - Murrain - The Effects of Managed Care on Minority and Indigent Populations (980374), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Havard Medical School - Cleary - Assessing Patient-Centered Care (Phase II) (20000218), 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Child Health Foundation of Boston - Flores - Access Barriers to Health Care for Latino Children (990127), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Child Health Foundation of Boston - Flores - Access Barriers to Health Care for Latino Children (990127), 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Community Service Society of New York - Molnar - Medicaid Managed Care Education Project (970357) (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (970648) (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (970648) - Proposal Development, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies (970648) - Grant Products (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Development of Quality Performance Measures for Women's Health (970651), 1997-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
- Gift of Life Foundation - Lopes (20000414) - Planning and Support for Diversity and Communication in Health Care: Addressing Race, Ethnicity, Language (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Picker Institute - Developing Patient-Centered Quality of Care Survey, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- New York Academy of Medicine - Fleishman - Racial Disparities in Health Care Delivery (20000413), 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)